<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Profile>
	<profile>
		<title>Resu'me</title>
		<title1>Resu'me Details</title1>
		<name>Geronimo Monsale</name>
		<birthday>March 12, 1999</birthday>
		<age>24</age>
		<address>Lupac, Boac, Marinduque</address>
		<phone>09389905884</phone>
		<email>ronmonsale09@gmail.com</email>
			<about>This website contains personal information about myself which can be used either business purposes and inquiries. I developed this website to just put all of my information in one place so others could know about myself more conveniently. Particularly my abilities and achievements.</about>
			<about1>As a networking enthusiast, I possess a deep understanding of various networking concepts, protocols, and technologies. Whether you're seeking advice on setting up a home network, troubleshooting connectivity issues, or exploring advanced networking solutions, I can assist you every step of the way.</about1>
			<about2>In the preceding section, I highlight my personal information that could assist someone in contacting me, including my email address and phone number for faster communication. This website also includes links to my social media accounts, such as my Instagram, Snapchat, Facebook, and Tiktok accounts.</about2>
				<skill>This shows my expertise in programming and markup language. It measures the percentage of my skills ranging from 0 to 100 percent.</skill>
					<resume>It is a formal document that a job applicant creates to itemize their qualifications for a position. A resume is usually accompanied by a personalized personal statement in which the applicant expresses interest in a specific job or company and draws attention to the most relevant details on the resume.</resume>
					<resume1>I am a highly skilled networking professional with a passion for connecting people, systems, and information. With a deep understanding of networking protocols, architectures, and technologies, I have developed a comprehensive skill set that allows me to design, implement, and optimize robust and secure networks..</resume1>
						<project1>I used the Python Pydroid 3 programming language to create a Mini Groceries store project. This is my very first project, one of my proudest accomplishments because it was the first time I had proposed something like it. It is a store in which aims to provide a convenient and efficient platform for customers to purchase groceries. With this project, customers can browse through a wide range of products, add them to their cart, and complete the purchase process seamlessly.</project1>
						<project2>Are you ready to dive into the fascinating world of Python programming and create an engaging quiz that will entertain and challenge your audience? Look no further! This comprehensive guide will take you through the step-by-step process of building a dynamic quiz using the powerful Python programming language.</project2>
						<project3>Are you ready to immerse yourself in the age-old game of Rock-Paper-Scissors and bring it to life using the power of Python programming? Look no further! This comprehensive guide will walk you through the step-by-step process of creating a dynamic Rock-Paper-Scissors game that will test your strategic thinking and provide hours of entertainment.</project3>
						<ads1>Introducing the captivating commercial video for LYN Tech Solutions, a leading IT company at the forefront of innovation. This visually stunning and engaging video showcases the expertise and cutting-edge solutions offered by LYN Tech Solutions, making it a must-watch for businesses seeking to elevate their digital capabilities.</ads1>
						<ads2>is a type of advertisement or promotional content specifically created to showcase and promote IT-related products, services, or solutions. These commercials are designed to appeal to businesses or individuals who are looking for technological solutions to enhance their operations, streamline processes, improve productivity, or address specific needs in the digital realm.</ads2>
							<service>To provide quality service and accommodate my clients, I must be adaptable and proficient as a service provider. The services offered are aimed at a specific audience. </service>
							<vid>One of my best skills is photo and video manipulation. It entails the transformation or alteration of a photograph using different tools and techniques to achieve the desired results.</vid>
							<comsupp>Computer support and services offer IT system diagnostics, troubleshooting, maintenance, and repair. It allows users to look for and receive computer maintenance and management services both locally and remotely.</comsupp>
							<softdev>Identifying, designing, installing, and testing a software system they created from the bottom up for a firm. It can range from developing internal programs to help businesses become more efficient to developing systems that can be managed to sell in the business sector.</softdev>
							<datalyst>Data analysts transform raw data into actionable insights and present findings to interested parties through one graphic form. Data analysts play an important role in daily operations across multiple sectors.</datalyst>
							<andrdev>Creates, programs, tests, and maintains apps and mobile platforms for smartphones, tablets, and laptops.</andrdev>
							<ux>Turn your apps into something that people enjoy and want to use. Prototyping, wireframing, user flows, mockups, visual design and design software, user research, and usability testing are all part of the process.</ux>
								<testimonial>  He's a remarkable individual who radiates warmth and kindness wherever they go. They have an infectious sense of humor that brings joy and laughter to any situation.</testimonial>
								<testimonial1>He's a skilled person who assists me in editing my videos and photos. She's good at photographing and styling, and I'm always impressed by her dedication.</testimonial1>
								<testimonial2>He's a nice person who always helps me to stay positive and take good photos. I had always admired her for her unique and uplifting attitude.</testimonial2>
	</profile>
</Profile>